Jesús Ruiz

Graphic Designer with +6 years of experience and Web Developer +2 years of experience

⊕ Lima, Perú

+51 935035069 • jesuizmail@gmail.com • https://linkedin.com/in/jesuiz



About Me

I have worked as a Graphic Designer for more than 6 years, specializing in Branding and Visual Identity. Now I focus on Web Development, accumulating +2 years of experience with real clients. I develop with Laravel and PHP, I also make well-optimized sites with Wordpress.

Work Experience

Jesuiz Design - Freelancer

2022 - Current

Graphic Designer & Web Developer

I execute digital solutions in Branding and Web Development internationally. Specifically Corporate Identity Design (Branding), Website Development, Ecommerce and Web Applications.

Clave Publicitaria - Printer's

2022 - 2023

Manager, Graphic Designer & Web Developer

I started as business manager and promoted the integration of new digital services complementing the Printing, Gigantography and Merchandising services.

Geotop - Surveying Company

2021 - 2021

Manager, Marketing Area

I designed all the company's audiovisual material for digital and physical environments. I developed a new Website with Wordpress and optimized all the company's other websites. I managed all the company's graphic design, as well as the edition and transmission of the monthly Webinars.

Techno Global - Printer's 2018 - 2021

Manager, Graphic Designer

I carried out designer activities related mainly to Advertising, Printing and Gigantography. After 6 months I led the advertising activities as Business Manager with 3 people in charge.

Education

Rodolfo Loero Arismendi Institute of Industrial Technology

2012 - 2015

Graphic Design Technician (Unfinished)

Certifications

EF Standard English Test: B2 Upper Intermediate EF SET Score: 59/100	2023	REST API course with PHP and MySQL Udemy	2023	Logical Thinking Course: Algorithms and Flowcharts Platzi	2023
PHP course with Laravel	2023	Introduction to PHP Frameworks Course Platzi	2023	REST API with PHP course Platzi	2023
PHP Basic Course: Installation, Fundamentals and Operators Plotzi	2023	Basic Computer and Informatics Course Platzi	2023		

Stack and Skills

